Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Administrative Assistant Files, 1962-2010; I.
  - Patricia Root, 1983-1996; 29.
    - Schedule, November 1986 (Box 640, Folder 15)
    - Schedule, March 1987 (Box 640, Folder 16)
    - Schedule, July 1987 (Box 640, Folder 17)
    - Schedule, November 1987 (Box 640, Folder 18)
    - Schedule, March 1988 (Box 640, Folder 19)
    - Schedule, July 1988 (Box 640, Folder 20)
    - Schedule, November 1988 (Box 640, Folder 21)
    - Schedule, April 1989 (Box 640, Folder 22)
    - Schedule, June 1989 (Box 640, Folder 23)
    - Schedule, July 1989 (Box 640, Folder 24)
    - Schedule, August 1989 (Box 640, Folder 25)
    - Schedule, September 1989 (Box 640, Folder 26)
    - Schedule, November 1989 (Box 640, Folder 27)
    - Schedule, January 1990 (Box 640, Folder 28)
    - Schedule, March 1990 (Box 640, Folder 29)
    - Schedule, April 1990 (Box 640, Folder 30)
    - Schedule, May 1991 (Box 640, Folder 31)
    - Schedule, August 1991 (Box 640, Folder 32)
    - Schedule, May 1996 (Box 640, Folder 33)
  - Doug Saltzman, 1997-2005; 30.
    Doug Saltzman served as executive director, Pittsburgh office, 1999-2006.
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 1997 (Box 640, Folder 34)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 1997 (Box 640, Folder 35)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1997 (Box 640, Folder 36-37)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-August 1997 (Box 640, Folder 38)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 1997 (Box 641, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 1997 (Box 641, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November-December 1997 (Box 641, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 1998 (Box 641, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 1998 (Box 641, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 1998 (Box 641, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 1998 (Box 641, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July-August 1998 (Box 641, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 1998 (Box 641, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1998 (Box 641, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-December 1998 (Box 641, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 1998-June 1999 (Box 641, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 2000 (Box 641, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-July 2000 (Box 641, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October-November 2000 (Box 641, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 2000 (Box 642, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February-March 2001 (Box 642, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 2001 (Box 642, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 2001 (Box 642, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June 2001 (Box 642, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 2001 (Box 642, Folder 6-7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 2001 (Box 642, Folder 8-9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-November 2001 (Box 642, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 2001 (Box 642, Folder 11-12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 2002 (Box 642, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 2002 (Box 642, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 2002 (Box 642, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 2002 (Box 643, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 2002 (Box 643, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 2002 (Box 643, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September-October 2002 (Box 643, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 2002 (Box 643, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January 2003 (Box 643, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, February-March 2003 (Box 643, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 2003 (Box 643, Folder 8-9)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May-June 2003 (Box 643, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 2003 (Box 643, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 2003 (Box 643, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 2003 (Box 643, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August-October 2003 (Box 643, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 2003 (Box 644, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, December 2003 (Box 644, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, January-February 2004 (Box 644, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March 2004 (Box 644, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, April 2004 (Box 644, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, May 2004 (Box 644, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, June-July 2004 (Box 644, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, July 2004 (Box 644, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, August 2004 (Box 644, Folder 9-12)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, September 2004 (Box 644, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, October 2004 (Box 644, Folder 14-15)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, November 2004 (Box 645, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh trip files, March-April 2005 (Box 645, Folder 2)
  - Kate Schramm, 1985-2010; 31.
    Kate Schramm served as: staff assistant, 2007-2008; caseworker, 2008; and administrative director, 2009-2010.
    - Get well cards, 1998 (Box 645, Folder 3)
    - Get well cards, 2008 (Box 645, Folder 4)
    - Office policy manuals, 1985-2006 (Box 645, Folder 5)
    - Teletown hall, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 6)
    - Thank you cards, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 7)
    - Town hall notices, 1996-2009 (Box 645, Folder 8)
    - Town hall quotes, 2007 (Box 645, Folder 9)
    - Website, About, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 10)
    - Website, Constituent services, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 11)
    - Website, Contact, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 12)
    - Website, Issues and legislation, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 13)
    - Website, News room, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 14)
    - Website, Pennsylvania connection, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 15)
    - Website, Student corner, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 16)
    - Website, Viting DC, 2010 (Box 645, Folder 17)
  - Susan "Vicky" Segal, 1992-2005; 32.
    Susan "Vicky" Segal served as: field representative, 2001-2004; caseworker, 2005-2006; executive director, 2007; and special assistant, 2008-2010.
    - AAI Corporation, 2000 (Box 645, Folder 18)
    - Abortions, Military, 1995 (Box 645, Folder 19)
    - Advanced encryption standard package, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 20)
    - Air defense altering device, 2000 (Box 645, Folder 21)
    - Air Products & Chemicals, 1999-2002 (Box 645, Folder 22)
    - Alcohol research, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 23)
    - Allegheny Ludlum, 2000 (Box 645, Folder 24)
    - ALQ-135, 1998 (Box 645, Folder 25)
    - Alternate technology, 1998-1999 (Box 645, Folder 26)
    - American Competitiveness Institutes defense appropriations, 2000 (Box 645, Folder 27)
    - American Federal of Government Employees, Defense Industrial Supply Center, 1998 (Box 645, Folder 28)
    - Analytical Graphics, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 29)
    - ANSAR, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 30)
    - Anthracite Council, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 31)
    - Anthrax vaccine, 1999 (Box 645, Folder 32)
    - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 645, Folder 33)
    - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 645, Folder 34)
    - Appropriations, 1992 (Box 645, Folder 35)
    - Appropriations, 1993 (Box 645, Folder 36)
    - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 646, Folder 1-2)
    - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 646, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 646, Folder 4-5)
    - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 646, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 646, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 646, Folder 9)
    - Armament Retooling and Manufacturing Support (ARMS), 1999 (Box 646, Folder 10)
    - Army Depot maintenance, 1994-1996 (Box 646, Folder 11)
    - Assembled Chemical Weapons Assessment Program, 1998 (Box 646, Folder 12)
    - Aydin Displays, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 13)
    - Azerbaijan, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 14)
    - BAE Systems, 2000 (Box 646, Folder 15)
    - Ballistic Missile Defense Organization, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 16)
    - BEAMHIT, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 17)
    - Bell Atlantic, Mine countermeasure, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 18)
    - Bell H-1 upgrade, 1998 (Box 646, Folder 19)
    - Biological agent research, 1998 (Box 646, Folder 20)
    - Biopure Corporation, 1999-2000 (Box 646, Folder 21)
    - Brashear, 2000 (Box 646, Folder 22)
    - Breast cancer, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 23)
    - Buy America, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 24)
    - Carelift International, 2000 (Box 646, Folder 25)
    - Carlisle Army Museum, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 26)
    - Carlisle Barracks, 1992-2000 (Box 646, Folder 27)
    - Cassidy, 1999 (Box 646, Folder 28)
    - CIA, 1995-1996 (Box 646, Folder 29)
    - Cephalon, 2001 (Box 646, Folder 30)
    - Chamberlain, 1999-2000 (Box 646, Folder 31)
    - Columbia hearing, 2000 (Box 646, Folder 32)
    - Comanche CH-47, 1998 (Box 646, Folder 33)
    - Comprehensive Test Ban Treaty, 1999 (Box 647, Folder 1)
    - Concurrent Technologies Corporation, 1999 (Box 647, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Budget Office (CBO) defense numbers, 1999 (Box 647, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Pig Book summary, 2001 (Box 647, Folder 4)
    - Construcciones Aeronauticas, 1999 (Box 647, Folder 5)
    - Cooperative threat reduction, 1999 (Box 647, Folder 6)
    - D3 International, 2001 (Box 647, Folder 7)
    - D5 missile, 2001 (Box 647, Folder 8)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 1993-1994 (Box 647, Folder 9)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 1999-2001 (Box 647, Folder 10-11)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 2002 (Box 647, Folder 12-17)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 2003 (Box 647, Folder 18)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 2004 (Box 647, Folder 19)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 2004 (Box 648, Folder 1-4)
    - Defense, Appropriation requests, 2005 (Box 648, Folder 5)
    - Defense, Association of Civilian Technicians, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 6)
    - Defense, Authorization bill, 1997 (Box 648, Folder 7)
    - Defense, Automated printing service, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 8)
    - Defense, Beinhart case, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 9)
    - Defense, Budget research, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 10)
    - Defense, Chinese human rights, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 11)
    - Defense, Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 12)
    - Defense, Grant announcements, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 13)
    - Defense, Iran, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 14)
    - Defense, Iraq, 1997-1999 (Box 648, Folder 15)
    - Defense, Kimmel & Short Resolution, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 16)
    - Defense, Military airshow requests forms, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 17)
    - Defense, Milosevic amendment, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 18)
    - Defense, Naval attractions, 1996 (Box 648, Folder 19)
    - Defense, Nominations, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 20)
    - Defense, Operation Sail 2000, 1997 (Box 648, Folder 21)
    - Defense, Pan Am 103, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 22)
    - Defense, Proliferation charts, undated (Box 648, Folder 23)
    - Defense, Reshaping American military forces, undated (Box 648, Folder 24)
    - Defense, Sexual abuse in the military, 1996 (Box 648, Folder 25)
    - Defense, Sexual harassment, Navy Reserve, 1994-1995 (Box 648, Folder 26)
    - Defense, Sexual trafficking, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 27)
    - Defense, John Shalikashvili, 1993 (Box 648, Folder 28)
    - Defense, United States Air Force (USAF) Office of Special Investigations, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 29)
    - Defense, United States Naval Academy cheating scandal, 1994 (Box 648, Folder 30)
    - Defense, USS Forrestal, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 31)
    - Defense, USS indianapolis, 1998-1999 (Box 648, Folder 32)
    - Defense, Warminster Township, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 33)
    - Defense, War Powers Resolution, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 34)
    - Defense, Weapons labs, 1994 (Box 648, Folder 35)
    - Defense, Willow Grove Naval Air Station, 1997 (Box 648, Folder 36)
    - Defense, Women in the military, 1993-1994 (Box 648, Folder 37)
    - Denied appropriation requests, 2001 (Box 648, Folder 38)
    - Department of Defense (DOD) cataloging consolidation, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 39)
    - Department of Energy, China labs, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 40)
    - DeVal, 1998 (Box 648, Folder 41)
    - Diabetes, 2000 (Box 648, Folder 42)
    - DKL Lifeguard, 1998-1999 (Box 648, Folder 43)
    - Drexel Applied Communication & Information Net, 1992-2001 (Box 648, Folder 44)
    - DRS Technologies, 2001 (Box 648, Folder 45)
    - EC-130/193rd visit, 1999 (Box 648, Folder 46)
    - Economic Development Council of Northeast Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 1)
    - Ejection seats, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 2)
    - Elckhorn Solingen, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Electronic commerce resources, 1996 (Box 649, Folder 4)
    - Emerson Electric, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 5)
    - Ethiopia, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 6)
    - Extrudehone, undated (Box 649, Folder 7)
    - Fast Ship, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 8)
    - Fatigue management, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 9)
    - Fidelity Tech Corporation, 1997 (Box 649, Folder 10)
    - Firefinder, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 11)
    - Flat panel display, 1999-2001 (Box 649, Folder 12)
    - Gender-integrated training, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 13)
    - General Dynamics, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 14)
    - Gentex helmets, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 15)
    - Glazo Smith Kline, Hepatitis B vaccine, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 16)
    - Golden Treasures: The Vatican Judaica Collection, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 17)
    - Guard requests, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 18)
    - H60 helicopter, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 19)
    - Haemonetics blood program, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 20)
    - Harris radios, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 21)
    - Hexel Corporation, undated (Box 649, Folder 22)
    - HUBS Telemedicine, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 23)
    - Integrated family of test equipment, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 24)
    - Intercooled recuperated gas turbine engine, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 25)
    - Impact Services Corporation, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 26)
    - Infusion Dynamics, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 27)
    - Intravenous membrane oxygenator, 1998-2000 (Box 649, Folder 28)
    - Israel, 1999-2001 (Box 649, Folder 29)
    - ITT, Singcars, 1999-2001 (Box 649, Folder 30)
    - Joint Surveillance Target Attack Radar System, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 31)
    - Keating housing, 1991 (Box 649, Folder 32)
    - Kids Peace, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 33)
    - Kosovo, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 34)
    - L3 Communications, undated (Box 649, Folder 35)
    - Lancaster Composite, 1997 (Box 649, Folder 36)
    - Lehigh Double Hull, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 37)
    - Letterkenny calibration lab technician, 1997-1999 (Box 649, Folder 38)
    - Lockheed Martin, 1997-2000 (Box 649, Folder 39)
    - Logics, 1996 (Box 649, Folder 40)
    - Lukens, 1996 (Box 649, Folder 41)
    - Marconi EA-6B, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 42)
    - Marine Machinery Composite Research Center, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 43)
    - Maritime Avionics Subsystems & Technology, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 44)
    - Maritime, Save Our Ships, 1994-1995 (Box 649, Folder 45)
    - Martin-Baker, Ejection seats, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 46)
    - Martin-Baker, MK 16, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 47)
    - Martin-Baker, I38 Escape System, 2000 (Box 649, Folder 48)
    - Medal of Honor, 1998-2000 (Box 649, Folder 49)
    - Medical acquisition transfer, 1998-1999 (Box 649, Folder 50)
    - Medicare subsidization, 1995-1996 (Box 649, Folder 51)
    - Medico Industries, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 52)
    - MEDTools, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 53)
    - Metals affordability, Initiative Consortium, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 54)
    - Mid-Atlantic Research Consortium, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 55)
    - Military construction, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 56)
    - Military health services, 1997 (Box 649, Folder 57)
    - Military Mobility Coalition, 1997 (Box 649, Folder 58)
    - Military pay freeze, 1993 (Box 649, Folder 59)
    - Military pay raise, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 60)
    - Military wives, 1994-1997 (Box 649, Folder 61)
    - MJU-52/B, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 62)
    - Morgan AM&T, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 63)
    - National Guard, 1998 (Box 649, Folder 64)
    - National Guard Bureau Nationwide Dedicated Fiber Optic Network Program, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 65)
    - National Military Museum Foundation Act, 1997 (Box 649, Folder 66)
    - National Missile Defense Act, 1997-1999 (Box 649, Folder 67)
    - National Technology Alliance, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 68)
    - Natural gas boiler, 1995 (Box 649, Folder 69)
    - Naval Supply Systems Command, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 70)
    - New Jersey battleship, 1999 (Box 649, Folder 71)
    - Northrop Grumman, 2001 (Box 649, Folder 72)
    - Northrop Grumman, ICR, 1997-1998 (Box 649, Folder 73)
    - Nuclear and chemical weapons, 1996-1997 (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1996 (Box 650, Folder 2)
    - Opportunities Industrialization Centers International, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Orbit, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 4)
    - Osteoporosis, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 5)
    - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Air National Guard, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania appropriations, 1998 (Box 650, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Educational Telecommunications Exchange Network, 1995-2000 (Box 650, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania National Guard, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania National Guard, Reports and Counter Drug Training Academy, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 11)
    - Penn State, Applied Research Lab, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia Industrial Development Corporation (PIDC), Navy yard, 1998-2000 (Box 650, Folder 13)
    - PIDC, Ship scrapping, 1996-2000 (Box 650, Folder 14)
    - Philadelphia Naval Ship Yard, 1997-1998 (Box 650, Folder 15)
    - Power Grid, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 16)
    - Prostrate cancer research, 1998 (Box 650, Folder 17)
    - Rapcon, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 18)
    - Red Zone Robotics, 1998-1999 (Box 650, Folder 19)
    - Robotic welding arm, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 20)
    - Robotics collaboration, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 21)
    - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 22)
    - Saint Francis College, 2001 (Box 650, Folder 23)
    - Sage Technologies, 2001 (Box 650, Folder 24)
    - Science Applications International, 1998-2001 (Box 650, Folder 25)
    - SERV-SMART, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 26)
    - Shipyard, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 27)
    - Silicon Power Corporation, Malvern, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 28)
    - Silk Road Bill, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 29)
    - Singcars, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 30)
    - Small arms fire control, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 31)
    - Space-based infared system letter, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 32)
    - Space policy, 1994 (Box 650, Folder 33)
    - Submarine industry, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 34)
    - Reverend Leon Sullivan, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 35)
    - Sultech, 2000 (Box 650, Folder 36)
    - Swiss Munitions, 1998 (Box 650, Folder 37)
    - TACOM/JAYS, 1996-1997 (Box 650, Folder 38)
    - Tensiodyne, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 39)
    - Terrorism amendment to defense appropriations, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 40)
    - Theater high altitude area defense, 1997 (Box 650, Folder 41)
    - Timken, 2001 (Box 650, Folder 42)
    - Title XI Ship Loan Guarantee Program, 2000 (Box 650, Folder 43)
    - Tobyhanna Army Depot, 1995-1999 (Box 650, Folder 44)
    - Tracor, 1998 (Box 650, Folder 45)
    - Tremont Medical, 2001 (Box 650, Folder 46)
    - UH-60L Black Hawk, undated (Box 650, Folder 47)
    - Ukraine meeting, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 48)
    - Unemployment compension for military personnel, 1994 (Box 650, Folder 49)
    - United Defense, 1997-2000 (Box 650, Folder 50)
    - U.S. Army Reserve and Guard, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 51)
    - U.S. Army School of the Americas, 1998 (Box 650, Folder 52)
    - U.S.-Japan Industry and Technology Management Training Program, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 53)
    - Uniformed Services Employment and Reemployment Rights Act, 1994-1998 (Box 650, Folder 54)
    - University of Pennsylvania tech research, 1997-1998 (Box 650, Folder 55)
    - V22 Osprey, 1993-1999 (Box 650, Folder 56)
    - Vectored thrust ducted propeller, 1995-1999 (Box 650, Folder 57)
    - VibroMeter, 2000-2001 (Box 650, Folder 58)
    - Villanova, 2001 (Box 650, Folder 59)
    - Wade Papers, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 60)
    - War crimes bill language, 2000 (Box 650, Folder 61)
    - Washington Square, 1995 (Box 650, Folder 62)
    - West Chester University, 2002 (Box 650, Folder 63)
    - Wilkes-Barre Veterans Administration Medical Center, 1995 (Box 650, Folder 64)
    - XenoTechnix, 1999 (Box 650, Folder 65)
    - Zinc, 1993 (Box 650, Folder 66)
  - Gil Stein, 1966-2000; 33.
    Gil Stein served as counsel, Philadelphia office, 1998-1999.
    - Articles and accomplishments, 1997-1998 (Box 650, Folder 67)
    - Constituent mail, 2000 (Box 650, Folder 68)
    - Independent Counsel case, 1997 (Box 651, Folder 1)
    - Legal, Articles, Arlen, 1994 (Box 651, Folder 2)
    - Legal, Articles, Bender, 1990 (Box 651, Folder 3)
    - Legal, Articles, Brickey, 1982 (Box 651, Folder 4)
    - Legal, Articles, Bucy, 1991 (Box 651, Folder 5)
    - Legal, Articles, Cohen, 1992 (Box 651, Folder 6)
    - Legal, Articles, Fisse, 1983 (Box 651, Folder 7)
    - Legal, Articles, Fisse, 1990 (Box 651, Folder 8)
    - Legal, Articles, Hager, 1989 (Box 651, Folder 9)
    - Legal, Articles, Hare, 1990 (Box 651, Folder 10)
    - Legal, Articles, Khanna, 1999 (Box 651, Folder 11)
    - Legal, Articles, Koenig and Rustad, 1998 (Box 651, Folder 12)
    - Legal, Articles, Kraakman, 1984 (Box 651, Folder 13)
    - Legal, Articles, Lederman, 1985 (Box 651, Folder 14)
    - Legal, Articles, Metzger, 1984 (Box 651, Folder 15)
    - Legal, Articles, Packman, 1998 (Box 651, Folder 16)
    - Legal, Articles, Rustad, 1992 (Box 651, Folder 17)
    - Legal, Articles, Weisman, 1993 (Box 651, Folder 18)
    - Legal, Articles, Zipperman, 1991 (Box 651, Folder 19)
    - Legal, Book chapter, undated (Box 651, Folder 20)
    - Legal, Case text, Bonnar et al. v. United States, 1971 (Box 651, Folder 21)
    - Legal, Case text, Cardona v. Power et al., 1966 (Box 651, Folder 22)
    - Legal, Case text, Citing references, 1999 (Box 651, Folder 23)
    - Legal, Case text, Ketzenbach et al. v. Morgan et ux., 1966 (Box 651, Folder 24)
    - Legal, Case text, White v. Ford, 1998 (Box 651, Folder 25)
    - Legal, Case text, White v. Ford, Materials, undated (Box 651, Folder 26)
    - Legal, Case text, White v. Ford, Retrial denial, undated (Box 651, Folder 27)
    - Legal, Newsclips, 1999 (Box 651, Folder 28)
    - Legal, Sent to blank, 1998 (Box 651, Folder 29)
    - Legal, Specter, 1994-1999 (Box 651, Folder 30)
    - National Journal, 1999 (Box 651, Folder 31)
    - Newsclips, 1997-1998 (Box 651, Folder 32)
    - Office, 1997-1998 (Box 651, Folder 33)
    - Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 651, Folder 34)
    - Sports, Baseball antitrust bill draft, 1996 (Box 651, Folder 35)
    - Sports, Constituent letters on baseball antitrust bill, 1996 (Box 651, Folder 36)
    - Sports, Franchise relocation articles, 1997 (Box 651, Folder 37)
    - Sports, Franchise relocation bill, 1996 (Box 651, Folder 38)
    - Sports, Franchise relocation information, 1996 (Box 651, Folder 39)
    - Sports, Judiciary Committee hearing, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 1)
    - Sports, Newsclips, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 2)
    - Sports, Resolution of baseball antitrust bill, 1994-1997 (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - Sports, Sportsbeat interview, 1984 (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Sports, Mike Tyson, 1997 (Box 652, Folder 5)
    - Topical Congressional Records, 1999 (Box 652, Folder 6)
    - Travel expenses, 1998-1999 (Box 652, Folder 7)
    - Unfair trade practices, Background and notes, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 8)
    - Unfair trade practices, Newsclips, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 9)
    - Unfair trade practices, Senate bill and speech drafts, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 10)
    - Unfair trade practices, Uruguay Round, 1994 (Box 652, Folder 11)
    - Unfiled, 1997 (Box 652, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers District Observer, 1999 (Box 652, Folder 13)